Subscribe to Smart Mandsaur
News Channel and press the bell to
get our latest video.
First of all, Hello Friends, Sajjan Kumar, and you are watching
this video, so in this video
I will tell you how you
can create your period password,
as it used to be Maheshwari, if you have
invested in Extra ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund,
then if you take out the statement, then
you can take out the statement in this way, okay, it was
told in this video, so here you
can send your statement to your mail here, you
can see here that this mail
is opened and here I have just received the mail, just a
while ago, the statement of ICICI
Prudential Mutual Fund has been
given to me, you
can see here that if I open this video, then what is
this password
protector, okay, I will have to
click on the passbook, then it will open,
it has been told in this video, so
many people did not know the password,
so in this video I will tell you how you can
create the password here,
that I  Okay, so here you can see
that it is itself written that
how can you create a password, okay, an
example is given here, these 123 people died,
so let's understand here, so
how do you create a password here,
if your name and here you can see that
if your name, for example, the
example is also given here, the
name of your village is Aditya Roshan, okay,
and the date of birth of the key is given as 75 75,
so what will be your password for Aditya Roshan,
you have to take the fourth alphabet, which
alphabet, so Aditya's name is DIT, so
here the key for your password, but
it is in lower case, okay, write it in lower case,
that is your date of birth, 75 75 means
seven my 75, so 795 will be written as zero seven
zero five here, that will be your four
digit password, so you will have the first
four digits, those will be your alphabets, the
beginning of your name, that will be your
alphabets in lower case, okay, and then
later your  There will be four judges of the date of birth,
you earn your day and mantra,
which date, then definitely the importance of Amitabh along with
zero five, therefore your password will be
Aditya 705, so the commission will be of your time,
okay, if your name and date of
birth is mentioned, then you can create it in this way,
if in any case
your date of birth is not available, then
what will happen to you is that the PIN number of your
PAN card, it is possible that in the mutual
fund, more than one person has
invested in the same mutual fund, okay, it can be a
combined account, so here the
donation of you is of the first holder only, it is considered
here, for example, if there are
two people Ram and Shyam, then the
password will be created here only for Ram, then it will be created according
to Ram, okay, so in
this way, if your date
of birth is not mentioned here, then the second
way of creating your password is that you have to
click on the PAN number of your PAN card, okay,
but you have to fill the PIN number in lower case,
what alphabets are there in the PAN number, so
You have to fill the alphabet in lower case, okay,
like if you write
Shravan here and you have taken it wearing it,
ABCD back 12345, okay, this is
someone's PAN card, if you have a PAN card
number, then the password you have to create is
CM, but you have to
write it in lower case, look ABCD, and you have
written it among your people, okay, so the second
way is this, and the
third way of creating a password is that if your PAN card and
your date of birth are not registered, then the
third way is your name and your
Jio 4G phone number, okay, now you
can create it by combining them, so
if your name is Aditya Roshan, then
you have to update the first four digits, Aditya,
and here you have to take the follow number, like the phone number
is given, 12345 723, here you have to
take four digits, so this will become your eight digit
password, in this the first four will be
your name and the last four will be your
follow number,
but you have to fill it in lower case,
okay, now like these are our three
ways, you can create a password, we get a
message here  I have given this to you and
I click on the PDF statement here.
Now we have asked for the password. Okay, so
I click here. For
example, my name is Hemant. Okay, what do I have to
write as PM and like this, my
date of birth is 500th July, what will you
write, 2054th July 2017. So I write it here. So
here I click on the bar pass automatically.
My name is Hemant. The
first four alphabets of the mantra are in lower case,
which is the date of birth. So, here the
four digit date of birth of the thing is called. And here you
can see that the statement here
is called. So there are two or three
ways here. You can do it in any way. If
you remember your PAN card, then
click on the PAN card number,
but in that you have to print the update log.
Okay, with this your step is done here.
If you get this, then
subscribe to Ayurveda India's channel. Here you find something like this daily.
If you turn on the alert so that you can get the
correct video notifications.